dntrade.com.au 2018-03-15

# DNTrade Privacy Policy - DNTrade

**1\. About**

This document explains how we collect, use and disclose your personal information in connection with our services. In this document when we use the term “we” or “us” it is a reference to Hypercraft ABN 75 172 062 699. Our website operates as a domain name and technology forum.

**2\. Collection**

2.1. Generally, the only personal information we collect about you is that which you choose to tell us, or the personal information which we obtain from others.

2.2. We may also collect information from a friend, reseller or someone who refers us to you, or through your use of our website.

2.3. We collect personal information which we consider relevant in providing and promoting our sponsors and advertisers goods and services to you, our own goods and services to you, and for operating our website.

2.4. The type of information we collect includes, your name, address, telephone number, and your computer’s IP address.

**3\. Use**

3.1. We use your personal information to provide our goods and services to you (including your participation in the forum) or to have one of our sponsors or advertisers provide goods and services to you.

3.2. We may also use your personal information to promote and market goods and services to you, to maintain and develop our business systems including other websites we operate, to provide customer service, for traffic analysis, and to comply with the law.

3.4. If you do not provide us with all or part of the personal information we require, it may prevent us from carrying out the things we have stated in this Policy.

3.5. If you receive promotional material you may choose to ‘opt out’ of receiving this information, just let us know.

**4\. Disclosure**

4.1. We will not sell your personal information without your consent, unless we sell or assign our business or any part of it.

4.2. We may choose to disclose your personal information to our sponsors or advertisers, contractors, our agents, government authorities, our advertising service providers and any other party who may assist us in providing goods or services to you, or in promoting or marketing our goods or services (or those of our sponsors or advertisers) to you, or any party who purchases or seeks to purchase our business (or any part of it including a website).

**5\. Cookies**

5.1. Sometimes we use cookies to track your internet browsers behaviour, and also to store your favourite settings on our website.

5.2. A cookie is a small file we store on your computer which holds the information we outlined in clause 5.1. Every time you visit our site we can view this information.

5.3 Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to (a) serve ads on our website; and (b) serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website.

5.4 Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

5.5 Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the ads preference manager or by visiting aboutads.info.

**6\. Safeguards**

6.1. We store your information in both electronic form and paper form.

6.2. We take all reasonable precautions to protect these records from misuse or unauthorised access by using physical, electronic and procedural safeguards.

6.3. It is our practice to destroy, delete or de-identify your personal information when it is no longer needed, but we must keep your files for the period required by law, after which time they may be destroyed.

**7\. Access**

7.1. When you provide us with personal information (or other third parties) provide us with personal information, we assume that it is correct unless you tell us otherwise.

7.2. Unless we know that personal information is incorrect, we cannot correct it. You can assist us, by telling us when the information we hold has changed and is no longer accurate.

7.3. If you wish to access the personal information we hold about you, you can do so by making a request to us. You can [contact us.](https://www.dntrade.com.au/content/contact-us)

**8\. Feedback**

8.1. We welcome any questions or comments and invite you to contact us.

8.2. We may amend this policy from time to time, to make sure that it is accurate and up to date.

8.3 You can contact us as follows [via email](https://www.dntrade.com.au/content/contact-us) or By Post: DNTrade, P.O Box 2061, Hotham Hill, Victoria, 3051.
